Okay, it is efficiently chilled, just brought it out of the refrigerator.
It was in there about twenty five minutes or so.
And you can pop it in the freezer if you need to, that's okay too.
You'll see that it's not even.
We poured it in and it was smooth, and now it looks like a rough rugged terrain that you would need a four wheel drive to go over.
But that's okay.
Fudge is homemade, at least it should be, so that's okay, not a big deal.
I personally don't care what my fudge looks like as long as it tastes good.
It even has a little ridge right here that cracked, you know, not, didn't crack but it has a little ridge that broke off.
That's okay.
Tastes dearly, ooh, okay.
So that's what you look for, just nice solid fudge.
Again, put it in the freezer if you need to.
I will say that if you want to take this with you somewhere, try to keep it in a frig.
You know if you take it to the office maybe as a little dessert after your lunch, that's a great idea.
Just pop it back in the frig when you get to work.
Because again that coconut oil is very sensitive to temperature.
So, it's perfectly congealed for me and solidified but as soon as I'm done you know, cutting it and showing you what it looks like I'm going to put it back in the freezer.
So just keep that in mind.